what up scobie's
a few people too
keep it light yeah
good plan it's kind of like pair to like
Honda's you might get carplay papa
oh no don't car politically they're
working periscope Oh for safety this
functions not available Oh excellent
cool no ok guys test drove a Cadillac
ct-6 with supercruise and so first we
get it anywhere like it I engaged here
can I engage we are driving we drive
over to route 1 I engage it on route 1
and I'm like yeah the first it
disengaged around us around a turn it
disengaged around a turn took it took a
solid two or three minutes to get the
system to even recognize that it was on
a freeway yeah and it was even when it
was engaged it was it didn't feel great
but then but then we got on the highway
we got on the highway we got on on 280
big clear open I wouldn't say the
quality was a fifth of Honda sensing I
would say it was like on par with like
Honda sensing unlike unlike route 1 but
then we got on the highway but then we
got on 280 um you know where the bends
are pretty shallow and it was flawless
it was no super cruise doesn't need
counter HD maps on huge multi-lane
highways it is absolutely flawless it
didn't so first off it doesn't wobble
both autopilot and open pilot wobble in
the lane you don't understand how good
it feels when it doesn't wobble um we
see it on the gyros okay
it's literally just edge
Oh bad a/c noise ah they don't like the
AC nose um yeah no no no ping-pong yeah
we turned it off we turned it off for
good but why do open pilot not of how
did GM do it it's a good question you
guess oh we got it we got a good way of
lava we got to get serious about beating
the evils of wobble so one way they
might have done it
is they have maps so they know the exact
angle the car is supposed to be at at
all times they don't have light are they
are using a camera to spot the lanes a
GPS and a map
behind us yeah
[Applause]
have you tried a very long turn you've
experienced some minor oscillations I
thought it was I thought it was
absolutely flawless on the highway where
his design we did get him so there was
an exit it was an exit and I'm like you
know you have his problem at all upon
autopilot where it kind of goes for the
exits um it didn't go for the exit but
it disengaged it disengaged
it just it wobbles the seat it turns red
yes surprising from GM I was very happy
with what supercruise I was impressed
and it just you know we have to do
better
wobbling
it's just something so solid about
superfoods yeah I was very much even
through the curves it was really dead
center in the lanes yeah like right here
you see a little bit of I'm gonna whop
that wobble so Chris doesn't do that
it's light so we're driving here on open
pilot and syndics I'm past economy Prius
waffles a loss I'm super crews using
Mobileye they use Bob like they use
mobile I and then they use they made a
custom HD map of all the highways so the
big downside of supercruise is where it
will engage so open pilot will engage
absolutely anywhere we just trust the
user and then that bit there's overshoot
on turns too
[Music]
we can we can be better we can we can be
better
you don't have the Prius interface mods
no no no no this is this is more of a
limitation about the pilot we have ideas
about how to really just fix all the
longitudinal control was worse than ours
there are longitudinal control I mean
every every single system is good on the
highway when there's like five mile an
hour speed differentials no I don't
think it's how mobilize doing it I don't
think they're using that I think they're
using just just the lanes really it's
detecting lanes from mobile I and it's
using PhD maps
yeah yeah so I have an idea that once
you have a gray panda by the end of the
year you've gone one of the cars that we
really try to tune well I will kill
wobble I want it to feel as good as
supercruise little gender and she maps
the lanes and will really just say okay
you have to stay in the exact center of
the car we have precise localization we
have to just do it um open pilots
longitudinal is is better we came up
behind it wasn't a fully stopped car it
was a car that stopped going at about
forty five and the braking was way too
late it was maybe it started breaking
maybe a half second before I would have
interviewed which is not good
how does camera interpret light our base
maps on chokers
so I think they've made very precise
maps of where all the lanes are and then
they just use those lane maps I'm gonna
look more into it I also bought a
subscription to the GM service manual
this morning so a few inches things
about supercruise it uses a forward
radar it uses four corner radars and it
uses a camera all connected my Flex
right that a young fan I know it's
getting hot though I mean
summers coming forth so sorry Scott it
off you know
these phones are not designed for this
but phones and our design yeah both of
the fan are designed for this yeah guys
yeah you know what will we understand
the unfair noise is one of the tiny
demerits of the e on the near gap it
wasn't set on your gap I couldn't even
see how much of the car I drove cost
should we show that no I don't think we
should show the price thank you can you
can look up the price of a Cadillac ct-6
I think it's me into the dealership show
the price I would get radicular quote
there's some chance we'll buy this
subject if this weekend I have a fit
what we have to go back to the board of
course late limits yeah you guys are
gonna see ready to ready player one
today I'm excited
you don't care about the fan noise yeah
no we should let me just okay it's like
everything that's a little bit bad about
our product we should do better and we
will do it better that's right next
product has a large fans although is it
like a symmetrical fan technology like
the MacBook you know the MacBook with
latest MacBook sat Retina display the
fans for like asymmetrical so that they
don't make noise this is a huge point in
the keynote I'm not sure that's patented
I think we're just going with the big
fans big is the way to go it works no
but actually a lot of that um fan noise
that we can probably fix with policy
certainly I think the fan policies a
little bit too aggressive yeah because
it's based on the CPU temperature it's
not really based on the heat sink
temperature right hmm I mean do you have
a lot of sensors yeah
sliding to were sliding really cool of
that work you guys do you guys like the
sliding or do you guys like the tapping
to make that appear and disappear that's
okay okay guys this is more responsive
than any automotive you I think we got
to do slide on tap it was easy
they were mostly voting for tap honestly
if you just like slap the screen
because yeah this isn't how you usually
come to work
yeah it's water on a timer oh yeah it's
on a timer to retract is that how we do
it
mmm timer to attract time when you
retract there's no well no if I just
feel like that it'll time does it
eventually oh no we don't have a timer
it's a sickie
it's sticky okay yeah cool
it's full screen mode speed related or
that's interesting hmm that's a good
idea when you're stopped we could bring
up your applications and status yeah I
kind of like I mean even when I'm
stopped
I think the fullscreen view is really
beautiful so I think I think loft how
whatever mode you want to be in it's
just a tap or swipe away well we'll give
you guys a little hint not all the
screen real estate will stay for the for
the camera we have something else if you
want to do it that's case something
that's gonna be right oh my god right
there is so good like when you look at
like you know guys the real reason
Cadillac having flex right now I don't
want any flexor that's it that's a
demerit if it didn't have flex pay I'd
be more likely to buy it
what's the name of that cab you mean the
comment and idea
that's a comedy a young running the
latest open pilot all car yeah talk are
coming soon know
honestly the other reason that I'm we're
probably not gonna buy the Cadillac is
there's no OTA updates that system will
never get better they're never going to
add support for the new roads maybe a
map such as Waze well my ways
forgot my stabilizer
let's go be like the stabilized
the subtle green is nice it's easy to
tell the engagement now I engaged no OTA
through OnStar no GM cars don't OTA
the Caddy doesn't add to the portfolio
the value of the other cars you've added
yeah we're not that rich guys you all
know if you could watch this pyro script
you know we did come into some money
recently but not enough for a Cadillac
all right so that has been my review how
much let's just say north of $80,000 the
maps can be updated not the software
it's possible they could add more roads
with a map update but I don't trust that
house breaking so good yeah our
longitudinals definitely but yeah
they're ladder on the highway
top notch so that's been my review of
super cruise I'm here with Andy hey we
are common eye and this is Ariana and
you should buy one at shop a calm day i
there was a comment a sound saying get
you 70 catch yeah I believe he goes down
to 70 so the car that we were looking at
how to infotainment package it also had
that was it I mean I also didn't really
negotiate the price we could always come
back the second time and the girl she
hit the price but all thanks for
watching email you where if he is real
oh to get of 70 K I don't know I don't
know all the stick on don't get me
started on stickers on windows HDR focus
update tonight well I'm gonna see the
movie I don't know
[Laughter]
later Kalahari